export const Questions = [
  {
    id: Math.random(),
    question: "2u32 + 2u32 =",
    correctAnswer: "4u32",
    wrongAnswers: [
      "2u64",
      "4u64",
      "2u32"
    ]
  },

  {
    id: Math.random(),
    question: "Which of these can be stored publicly?",
    correctAnswer: "Address",
    wrongAnswers: [
      "View Key",
      "Private Key",
      "Seed Phrase"
    ]
  },

  {
    id: Math.random(),
    question: "I like ...",
    correctAnswer: "Aleo",
    wrongAnswers: [
      "Aloe",
      "Alex",
      "Alice"
    ]
  },
  
  {
    id: Math.random(),
    question: "what is not related to <a.aleo> Program here?",
    correctAnswer: "ERC20.sol",
    wrongAnswers: [
      "main.leo",
      "a.in",
      "program.json"
    ]
  },
  {
    id: Math.random(),
    question: "The highest rank for Aleo Ambassador is",
    correctAnswer: "Maestro",
    wrongAnswers: [
      "Voyager",
      "Big Bad Boss",
      "Lord"
    ]
  },
  {
    id: Math.random(),
    question: "snarkos developer execute",
    correctAnswer: "Calling Aleo Program",
    wrongAnswers: [
      "Deploying Aleo Program",
      "Reseting you PC",
      "Calling Aleo Team"
    ]
  },
  
  {
    id: Math.random(),
    question: "The right place to say hi is?",
    correctAnswer: "#gm﹠gn ",
    wrongAnswers: [
      "#русский",
      "#українська ",
      "#discussion "
    ]
  },
  
  {
    id: Math.random(),
    question: "What LEO Client command right?",
    correctAnswer: "leo run",
    wrongAnswers: [
      "leo can",
      "leo fun",
      "leo ban"
    ]
  },
  
  {
    id: Math.random(),
    question: "Who is the CTO of Aleo?",
    correctAnswer: "Howard Wu",
    wrongAnswers: [
      "Alex Pruden",
      "Viviane Ford",
      "Me"
    ]
  },
  
  {
    id: Math.random(),
    question: "Decentralized Operating System for ZK Applications is?",
    correctAnswer: "snarkOS",
    wrongAnswers: [
      "Aleo SDK",
      "LEO Client",
      "zkEVM"
    ]
  },
  
  {
    id: Math.random(),
    question: "Official Aleo site is?",
    correctAnswer: "aleo.org",
    wrongAnswers: [
      "aleo.build",
      "aleo.network",
      "aleo.tools"
    ]
  },
  
  {
    id: Math.random(),
    question: "Awesome wallet for Aleo is?",
    correctAnswer: "Leo Wallet",
    wrongAnswers: [
      "MetaMask",
      "Phantom",
      "Bag"
    ]
  },
]

export const topics = [
  "Biology",
  "Maths",
  "English",
  "History",
]
